原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     西·查    想念Gallifrey的Wholock
后期     累
总监     累
黄石
第三季  第八集
泰特
Tate.
下去吃早餐吧
Let's get down for breakfast.
他在马场
He's at the fairgrounds.
他和你父亲一起在看赶牛的
He's watching the cowhorse guys with your father.
赶牛的
Cowhorse guys?
靠
Oh, Jesus.
他在买马
He's horse shopping.
他应该享受一下退休生活了
Well, he should enjoy his retirement.
如果马能让他开心  那就应该买
If a horse makes him happy, he should buy it.
我爸还没退休
My dad ain't retired.
他的日常是
Here's what he does all day:
和泰特一起散步  一起骑马
he goes on walks with Tate, he goes riding with Tate,
一起钓鱼
goes fishing with Tate.
一起打棒球
He plays baseball with Tate.
同时  你每天要工作16个小时来完成他的工作
Meanwhile, you're working sixteen hours a day doing his job.
其实是他的两份工作
Both of his jobs, actually.
他退休了
The man is retired.
你今天刷房子吗
You painting the house today?
你为什么穿成这样
Why you dressed like that?
做些志愿者工作
Doing some volunteer work today.
洗车吗
Like a car wash?
差不多吧
Something like that.
你该庆幸他去买马了
You're lucky he's horse shopping.
当你父亲这样的人退休后
When a man in your father's position retires
通常会找个25岁的女朋友
he usually gets a 25 year-old girlfriend,
然后给她买跑车和公寓
then buys them a sports car and a condo.
25岁的女朋友加上跑车
25 year-old girlfriend, a sports car,
还有公寓反而更便宜
and a condo would be cheaper.
相信我
Trust me.
靠  你好美
Damn, you look good.
去解救你父亲吧
Go save your father from himself.
你要买它吗
You gonna buy him?
也许吧
Maybe.
但我们家已经有很多马了
But we already have a lot of horses at home.
家里很多人要用马
I got a lot of using horses.
在农场赚钱有两种方法
There's two ways to make money on a ranch:
卖牛和推销马匹
sell cattle and market horses.
我没有马要推销
I don't have a horse to market.
怎么推销马匹
How do you market a horse?
让它们比赛  这样买家可以观察马匹的能力
Send them down the road and see what they can make.
所以我今天不只是在看马
So, I ain't just looking at the horse today.
还在看骑手
I'm looking at the rider, too.
这些是最厉害的骑手吗
Are these the best riders?
世界上最厉害的
Best in the world.
马不错  鲍勃
Nice horse, Bob.
谢谢  先生  这匹马挺不错的
Thank you, sir, he's a good one.
如果我买下它  你会让它继续比赛吗
You gonna keep him on the road if I buy him?
我想好好享受生活
You know, I'm trying to enjoy my life.
如果你买了  那就你来吧
If you buy him, you show him.
我就算了  我也想好好享受
Don't wanna show him. I'm trying to enjoy mine, too.
这里有一个全是世界冠军的马场
You know, you've got an arena full of world champions out here.
闭上眼睛  扔根棍子都能打中一匹良驹
You could close your eyes, throw a stick, and hit a winner.
你想靠马赚大钱  就得学会这个
You wanna make big money on a horse, learn how to do that.
学习如何成为艺术家
Learn how to be an artist.
你准备让它抓牛还是赛马
You running her in the cow horse or the reining?
如果奖金够丰厚
I'd show her in a chariot race
我准备带它参加战车比赛
if there was enough prize money.
你还和特拉维斯·惠特利混在一起吗
You still pal around with Travis Wheatley?
操  我没那么傻了
Shit. Against my better judgement.
那个混蛋  如果你被困在流沙里
That son of a bitch... If you were stuck in quicksand
他会在把你拉出来之前收你绳子的钱
he'd charge you for the rope before he pulled you out.
肯定的
That's for damn sure.
不过在酒吧还是玩得很开心的
Sure a lot of fun at the bar, though.
这是他的特长
That's his special skill.
这些牛仔都愿意为你工作  你知道的
Any of those boys are going to work for you, you know that.
我想在海滩休假
I've got a beach in my sights
把脚趾埋进沙子里
I'm gonna stick my toes in the sand.
-给我留个位子  好吗  -没问题
- Save me a seat, would ya? - You got it.
他也没那么老  是吧
He don't look too done to me, does he?
爸  我们不需要
Dad, we do not need...
这匹马不错啊
That's a nice horse.
一家人的品位都这么贵啊
Expensive taste runs in the blood.
只有这样我爸才能弄到马
That's the only way my dad would get it
因为他穷的一批
'cause he's broke as hell.
少去工棚
Stay away from the bunkhouse.
准备上班吗
Headed to the office, huh?
嗯
Yeah.
调查挺快啊
Pretty quick investigation.
我只是去处理一些文件
I just wanna get through some paperwork.
现在还不能出去
Not really cleared to go back out just yet.
他们还好吧
Boys are all right, though?
死不了
They'll live.
你们在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
工作上的事
Just work stuff.
看那匹马  伙计
Wow, look at that horse, buddy.
莫妮卡还不知道
Monica doesn't know.
消息挺闭塞啊  毕竟
Pretty short sighted, considering...
报纸都登了
it's already in the... newspaper.
她不读报纸
She don't read that.
如果你想晚点再说
Well, if you want to talk about it later...
有什么好说的
What's there to talk about?
我觉得我们有很多话要说  儿子
I think there's plenty to talk about, son.
我得走了
Gotta go.
你知道去哪找我
You know where to find me.
你们为什么要打哑谜
Why were you guys talking in secrets?
我不来这套
I don't do that.
秘密就像心脏上的老茧
Secrets are like a callus on your heart.
老茧是什么
What's a callus?
感受一下  这里
Feel that, right there.
好硬
That's hard.
这就是老茧
That's a callus.
每个秘密都有这种感觉
And every secret feels just like that.
说多了  不久之后
Tell enough of them, and before long...
你的心脏就不会有任何感觉了
Your heart won't feel a thing.
因为是她引诱的
Because she baited them into it!
纽约的对冲基金经理都在做空我们
Every hedge fund manager in New York is shorting us now...
真假并不重要
It doesn't matter if it's true!
巨石正在滚下山
The boulder is rolling down the hill
而我却无能为力
and I can't do anything to stop it.
给股东们打个电话
Look, set a call with shareholders.
我们得开始回购
We need to start a buy back.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know...
我操
I fuck--
我知道
I know.
我们打个电话  在75块的时候收购
We'll set the call, and issue a tender offer at 75.
一旦价格有所转变
Once the price starts to turn,
就2.5万股一次买进舒瓦茨和梅耶的股票
start buying Schwartz and Meyer shares in blocks of 25,000.
一旦达到50万  就开始联系基金公司
Once you hit half a million, start reaching out to the funds.
我们今天就要消灭这个虫子
We are squashing this bug today.
搞什么
What in the...
又怎么了
What now?
我只想跟你握个手
Just wanna shake your hand.
谢谢
Thank you.
为什么
For what?
保护属于我们的东西
For protecting what's ours.
还冒着自己的生命危险
And for risking your life to do it.
唐尼
Donny...
他可没有享受过这种待遇
He never had that.
这些人尊重他  忠诚于他
He had their respect. He had their loyalty.
但是
But that...
我都不知道你管这叫什么
I don't even know what you call that.
我也不知道
I don't either.
感激吧
Gratitude, I guess.
那次开枪是合理的
That shooting was justified.
我的办公室不会质疑的
My office won't question it.
你也许该质疑一下
Well, you should probably question it.
我只是先和你说一下你会发现什么
I'm just letting you know what you're going to find out.
我需要一些建议  弟弟
I need some advice, brother...
前提是我还能这么叫你
If I can still call you that.
在你死之前  最好一直这么叫我
'Til the day you die you better never call me anything else.
山谷正在进行军备竞赛
There's an arms race going on in this valley,
武器就是土地
and the weapon is land.
市场股票拿到林务局一万两千英亩的租赁合同
Market Equities has a forest service lease
建一个滑雪度假村
on 12,000 acres to build a ski resort.
他们和联邦航空局签了租赁合同
They have a lease agreement with the FAA
建一个国际机场
to build an international airport.
他们指定的土地是12到32号的牧场
The Land they have earmarked are pastures 12 through 32.
-我们的土地  -我们的土地
- Of our land. - Our land.
我和州长  土地委员会
There is a meeting with the Governor, myself,
还有市场股票董事会要开个会
the land commission and the board of Market Equities next week.
事实上这次会议
Now, the fact that this meeting is even set
证明蒙大拿州政府想要这块地
means that Montana wants it.
我收到了市场股票的报价
I do have an offer from Market Equities
每英亩一万
at ten thousand per acre.
那两个牧场之间有五万英亩
There's fifty thousand acres between those pastures.
五亿美元
It's half a billion dollars.
如果我们拒绝这个提议
If we turn this offer down, then the attorneys
市场股票的律师将推动政府
for Market Equities are going to push the government
寻求土地征用权
to seek eminent domain.
我无法为州政府辩护  因为
I will be recused from representing the state because...
这是我们的土地
It's our fucking land.
公众需要工作  收入
There is public need: the jobs, the revenue...
有什么解决办法吗
Is there any kind of a solution?
我们卖给他们
We sell it to them.
现在农场的钱
Right now, the ranch has enough money
够付一年的税收和运营费用
to keep up with taxes and operations for another year.
也许两年
Maybe two.
然后我们还是要卖
Then we're selling anyway.
你都跟老爸解释过了吗
And you've explained all this to dad?
贝丝跟他告了我一状
Beth has poisoned me to him.
如果你跟他解释
And if you explain it to him--
他最不想听我说的就是数字
The last thing he wants to hear from me is numbers.
必须得由贝丝说
It has to come from Beth.
我能看看报价单吗
Can I see the offer?
这是口头协议
Well, it was a verbal agreement.
我得看到报价单  杰米
I need to see it, Jamie.
除非有报价单  不然她是不会相信的
She's not gonna believe it unless she sees it on paper.
哪怕是我说的
Even if it's coming from me.
嗯
Yeah.
能帮我接市场股票的威拉·海斯的吗
Can you get me Willa Hayes from Market Equities?
无服务
车坏啦
Broke down, huh?
嗯  散热器坏了
Yeah, it's the radiator.
应该是水管
The hose, I think.
你有多的吗
Don't have a spare, do you?
你要自己修吗
You gonna fix it all by yourself?
你有多的吗
Do you have a spare?
日产的应该没有
Not for a Nissan I don't.
但我可以送你去比林斯
But I can give you a ride up to Billings.
我要去那边
I'm headed that way,
那太好了
Yeah, that would be great.
上车吧
Climb in.
稍等
One sec.
舒瓦茨和梅耶
我们别无选择  鲍勃
We don't have a choice, Bob.
鲍勃  这就是你雇我的原因  好吗
Bob, this is what you pay me for, okay?
所以听我说
So just fucking listen to me.
到185块开始买看涨期权
I need you to buy puts at a strike of 185.
好吗  不要停
Okay? And do not stop...
明白了吗  不要停
Do you understand me? Do not stop.
嗯  我们股票有费用
Yeah, we have a charge on our stock.
市场股票
Market Equities.
你能把它弄掉吗
Can you get it out?
谢谢
Thank you.
我看起来像是要喝咖啡的人吗
Do I look like I need a fucking cup of coffee?
天啊
Oh God, uh...
这么不禁吓吗
Is that's all it takes to shake you?
你被解雇了
You're fucking fired.
-我  -是的  你被解雇了
- I'm... - Yes, you're fired.
去教瑜伽吧  你个废物
Go fucking teach yoga, you fucking pussy.
听起来你今天过得不错啊
Angela: Sounds like you're having quite the day.
你想赚钱吗
Yeah, you want make some money?
我爱钱
I love money.
媒体发布之前
All right, well, I'm telling you this
我先给你通个气
before the press release is out...
市场股票在买我们的股票
Market Equities is going for a run.
这可不妙啊
Well, that's not nice.
你喜欢哪个
Where's your preferred?
普通股
I go after the common.
舒瓦茨和梅耶
我不吃零食  贝丝  要吃就吃大餐
I don't take nibbles, Beth. I take bites.
现在是220块  亲爱的
Well this is at 220, Honey.
我打几个电话  看看谁饿了
Let me make a few calls and see who's hungry.
想想看  一周后我们就能成为搭档了
Just think, in a week we could be partners.
看看《市场观察》
Look at Market Watch.
市场股票集团试图恶意收购舒瓦茨和梅耶
这女人真有种  我们的价格呢
The balls on this woman. What's our number?
跌7块到64块
Down seven to sixty-four.
等我害这贱人被解雇后  我们把她招过来吧
After I get this bitch fired, we should hire her.
蒙大拿州检察长达顿
Attorney General Dutton of Montana.
有什么可以帮你
How can I help you?
没问题  你有邮箱吗
I can do that. Do you have an email?
一小时内就可以起草并发送过去
I can have it drafted and sent within an hour.
谢谢
Thank you.
涨到150块以后就全部抛掉  一股都别剩
After we get to 150, dump it. Every fucking share.
他定价合理吗
He priced right?
够合理了
Yeah, right enough.
你确定不带它参加比赛吗
Well, you sure you won't take him down the road?
我们有段时间没比赛了
It's been a while since we've done it.
其他人都忘了我们的存在
Rest of the world is forgetting we're here.
是时候提醒他们了
Time to remind them.
我不是让你把栗色马送去斯坦纳那里吗
Thought I told you to run that sorrel over to Steiner's.
我去了  他们不喜欢它
No, no, no, I did. They didn't like him.
它弓背还不够给力
He didn't buck hard enough for them.
-还不够吗  -嗯
- Didn't buck hard enough? - No.
我觉得够给力了
He bucked hard enough for me.
你说怎么办
Well, what do you want to do?
卖掉它吗
You want to put him through a sale?
不  它会被送去屠宰场的
No. He'll end up in a slaughterhouse.
不能因为它不想被骑  就杀了它吧
Can't have him killed just because he doesn't want to be ridden.
我也不想被骑
Hell, I don't want to be ridden either.
好吧  我会想办法的
All right, well, I'll figure it out.
就这样吗
That's it?
你还有什么想说的吗
Anything else you feel like discussing?
如果你想加入这个家庭
If you're joining the family can you please be the one person
你能当我面说出来吗
in it who fuckin' talks to me?
我爱她  先生
I love her, sir.
我会一直照顾她的
I'll always take care of her.
所以我答应了她
That's why I said yes.
你知道为什么
You know why, uh,
没人敢直接跟你说吗
people don't come and talk to you?
因为他们害怕会让你失望
'Cause they're scared they're going to let you down.
反正我害怕
I know I am.
如果你要娶贝丝
Well, if you're marrying Beth,
你已经证明了你无所畏惧
you've already proved you're not scared of anything.
嗯
Yeah. Yeah.
那匹马需要一个家
That horse needs a home.
但不是我的家
It just ain't mine.
-给它找个家  -好的
- Go find him one. - Yes, sir.
它不介意吗
He doesn't mind that?
当然不会  它很喜欢
Hell, no. He loves it.
对它来说就像糖果一样
It's like fucking candy to him.
这对它们的肠胃有好处
It helps their guts...
防止它们得溃疡和结肠炎
Keeps 'em from getting ulcers and from colicking.
最后一个
The last one.
吉米  去开拖车
Jimmy, go hook up the trailer
把栗色马装上  好吗
and load up that sorrel, will you?
等你弄完以后
When you're done doing what you're doing,
就上皮卡  罗伊德
come out to the truck, Lloyd.
为什么
What for?
我需要人陪我
I want some company.
你干嘛
What're you doing?
这上面有个地方  信号很好
There's a spot up here you can get great cell service.
我想着你可能想给家里打个电话
Figured you might want to call home.
让他们知道你的车坏了
Let them know you broke down.
我还是进城再打吧
I'd rather call from town.
不不  就在这上面
Oh, no, no, it's just right up here.
过去吧  那里信号很好
Walk right up there, we get great service.
你去吧  我留下
All right, you go ahead and I'll stay here.
走吧
Come on.
不要
Don't!
我真是不会明白
I'll never understand.
别挣扎了
Just let it happen!
-莫妮卡  -我没事
- Monica. - I'm fine.
- Monica. - I'm fine!
慢慢来
Slow everything down.
急救人员在战术中心  我让他们上来了
The EMS is at the tactical center. I'm having them come up.
你是个勇敢的女人
You're a brave woman.
还好你没打偏
Thank you for not missing.
我不会让你失望的
I wouldn't do that to you.
抱歉  我没注意
I'm sorry. I didn't realize.
靠
Oh, shit.
他们发现了遗骸
They found remains.
人们总说要做出改变
People talk about making a difference.
但他们没有
But they don't.
因为他们从不尝试
Because they don't try.
他们不愿意冒险
They don't risk.
你赌上了一切
You risked. Everything.
今天你做出了改变
And today you made a difference.
因为有传言
As rumors of an attempted takeover
舒瓦茨和梅耶投资公司将被收购
of the investment firm Schwartz and Meyer sent Wall Street
华尔街陷入疯狂  股价飙升110%到158块
into a frenzy, running that stock up 110% to 158 per share.
市场股票集团总裁威拉·海斯否认传言后
Market Equities Group CEO, Willa Hayes, dismissed the rumor
股价暴跌至开盘价的26%
and the stock plummeted down to 26 percent below its open...
有得必有失
Well, you win some, you lose some.
我是鲍勃·施瓦茨的助理
This is Bob Schwartz's assistant.
施瓦茨先生要飞去博兹曼
Mr. Schwartz is flying up to Bozeman and would like
明天下午三点
to meet with you tomorrow afternoon
和你在黄石俱乐部见面
at the Yellowstone Club. 3 p.m.
你觉得时间可以吗
Can you confirm that time is acceptable?
当然  女士
Fuckin' A, lady.
你拿的是什么
Whatcha got there?
等等  我换个说法
Wait, let me rephrase that--
杰米给了你什么
What did Jamie give you?
你不是说找个人陪你吗
Thought you said you wanted some company.
为什么
What for?
我们开了六个小时的车
We been driving for six hours
你他妈一个字都没说
and you ain't said a fuckin' word.
罗伊德  我在思考措辞
Lloyd, I'm trying to choose my words.
操  这么久都能写首歌了
Shit, shoulda been able to write the fucking song by now.
土地管理局
你正在进入普赖尔山野马范围
你个老好人
You old softy.
自从离开农场
Been kicking the shit out of this Bloomer
它就被折腾得不轻
ever since we left the ranch.
也该让它最后享受一下时髦的房车之旅  罗伊德
He deserves to have his last trailer ride in style, Lloyd.
放松
Easy, boy.
你好像不喜欢和我们住在一起  是吗
Didn't seem to like living with us, did you?
不得不说  我也这么觉得
I gotta say, the feeling is mutual.
希望你喜欢这里
Hope you like it better here,
因为你回不去了
'cause you ain't welcome back.
追求卓越
我要结婚了
I'm getting married.
我还在好奇你最近是怎么了
Yeah, I've been wondering what's up with you lately.
我需要伴郎
I need a best man.
凯斯是她弟
Kayce's her brother.
马上就是你的小舅子了
Fixin' to be yours.
你应该去问他
You should ask him.
也许吧  但我不想问
Probably so. But I ain't.
我在问你呢
I'm asking you.
你的车准备好了
They have your car ready.
他们知道怎么换水管  对吧
They know how to replace the hose, right?
我不想再经历一次了
I don't want to go through this again.
有人会护送你回农场
You'll have an escort to the ranch.
我不需要护送回牧场  只要
Don't need one an escort to the ranch, just, um...
要我打给凯斯吗
Would you like me to call Kayce?
我没告诉他
Didn't tell him I was doing this.
今天闹出这种事  我不知道还怎么告诉他
And based on how today worked out, I'm not sure how.
他是怎么跟你说的
How did he tell you?
跟我说什么
Tell me what?
不是一家人  不进一家门
It's no wonder we're married, huh?
我们的想法一模一样
We think exactly alike.
你有没有想过为什么山里有晰易
You ever wonder why there's leezards in the mountains
么有赊
but nee snikes?
没有
No.
但我很好奇你他妈在说啥
But I do wonder what the fuck you just said.
但我一直很好奇  所以
But I always wonder that, so...
停一哈
Hold the fucking gator.
什么
What?
你想裸泳吗
You wanna go skinny dipping?
裸泳
Skinny dipping?
你现在知道我在说什么了吧
You ain't wondering what I said now, are ya?
不  我们还要修围栏呢
No, we got a whole fence to fix.
围栏又不会跑
Fence ain't goin nowhere.
宝贝  脱光吧
Come on, baby. Let's get naked.
这是个测试
This is a test.
这只是个测试  好吧
Yeah, just a test. Yeah, okay.
管它呢
Fuck it.
看什么看  混蛋
Hell you looking at, fuckheads?
这里不是让你们免费看奶子的
This ain't no free titty show.
这个人的嘴也挺能说啊
What about the mouth on this one?
你帮她擦擦耳朵后面  说不定还能值点钱
You scrub her behind her ears she might be worth a twirl.
你们走错边了
You're on the wrong side of the fence.
今天对你来说
Looks like the whole world is on the wrong side
全世界都走错边了
of the fence for you today.
你们走吧
You need to move on now.
你们赶紧滚出我们的农场
Why don't you just go ahead and get the fuck off our ranch?
这是你的农场了吗
Oh, it's your ranch now. Is it?
你帮我给约翰·达顿带个口信
I want you to give John Dutton a message for me.
是吗  什么口信
Oh, yeah? What's that?
请把门关上
Close the door, please.
今天不顺吗
Rough day?
你今天过的怎么样
How was your day?
我每天过的都一样  宝贝
Mine are all the same, baby.
是吗  都一样吗
Are they? All the same?
你骗我的时候脑子里在想什么
What goes through your mind when you're lying to me?
保护我吗  保护什么呢
You're protecting me? From what?
你都干了那么多缺德事
After all I've seen you do.
但我不能生气  因为这就是我骗你的原因
But I can't be angry because that's why I lie to you.
-你撒了什么谎  -你撒了什么谎
- What did you lie about? - What did you lie about?
我不想告诉你是因为
I didn't want to tell you because
我每次的原因都一样
it's always the same story with me.
我总是处于需要杀人或被杀的境地
I'm always in a position where I need to kill or be killed.
现在还变成了我的工作
Hell, it's my job now.
我不想说  是因为
I don't want to say anything because...
我不想让你觉得我是个坏人
I don't want you to think I'm a bad man.
哪怕我会这么想
Even if I think it.
我不想让你这么想  因为如果你这么想
I don't want you to think it because if you think it,
那就是真的了
then it's true.
自从我认识你  这就是你的工作  凯斯
It's been your job since I've met you, Kayce.
我相信你杀人
And I believe in my heart that every man you killed
是为了让世界变得更安全
has made the world a safer place.
这就是我对自己杀人的感觉
That's how I feel about the man I killed.
我今天杀了一个人
I-I killed a man today.
这可不像是娇羞的新酿啊
That's not the glow of a blushing bride.
爸
Oh, Dad...
我几年前就被操的不会娇羞了
the blush was fucked out of me years ago.
靠
Jesus.
宝贝  我喜欢咱俩爷们的对话  但是
Baby, I love our man-to-man talks, but...
我们得建立一些界限
We need to set some goddamn boundaries here.
我没办法假装没听到  亲爱的
I can't unhear that, honey.
这是个比喻
It was a metaphor, sort of...
我给你看样东西
Look, I gotta show you something.
但在此之前  我想让你知道
But before I do, I want you to know this about me--
我知道你已经知道了  但我得再说一遍
I know you already know it, but I got to say it again.
我做的一切都是为了你
Everything I do is for you.
让你满意
To please you.
保护你
To protect you.
我可以用数据  事实  理性地告诉你
And I can tell you what I think is best,
我觉得什么是最好的
with data and facts and zero emotion,
但我会照你说的做
but I will do whatever it is you tell me to do.
好
Okay.
你相信这个提议是合法的吗
And you believe this offer is legitimate?
他们明天会电汇10%的定金
They will wire ten percent earnest money tomorrow
七天时间收尾
with a seven day close.
现在你可以告诉我  我为什么应该这么做
Now you're going to tell me all the reasons I should do it.
我不相信"应该"
I don't believe in should.
我只能告诉你不这么做的后果
All I'll tell you is the consequences of not doing it.
我只求你可以听我说
And all I ask is that you listen.
我会听的  亲爱的
I'll listen, honey.
如果你不接受
If you don't accept,
他们会向政府施压  征收这片土地
they will press the state to condemn the land.
他们会提出动议  让杰米无法为州政府辩护
They will file a motion to recuse Jamie from representing the State
因为他在农场享有经济利益
because of his financial interests in the ranch.
他们会找第三方律师
They will bring in outside counsel and Jamie,
而杰米  虽然我非常恨他
and how much I hate him,
但他是本州的诉讼律师
he is the litigator for the state,
他将无法为我们辩护
and he will no longer be available to us,
除非他辞职
unless he resigns.
就连我都能看出在这个特殊时期
And even I can see the value in having him in office
他任职的作用有多大
at this particular moment.
他们会征收这片土地
They will condemn this land
然后付给你15%的佣金
and they will pay you fifteen cents on the dollar.
如果这样
If that.
农场的剩余土地也会以类似的方式
And what remains of the ranch will be taken from you
从你手上被夺走
in a similar fashion,
这并不重要
which doesn't really fucking matter
因为房产税很可能
because the property taxes will most likely
会在接下来的三四年内侵蚀你的存款
erode your savings within the next three to four years.
我可以再撑个两年
Now I can cover them for a couple more,
但到头来  你只是在变卖土地
but in the end you're just selling off land
一边交税一边没有任何产出
to pay the taxes while making nothing.
这个循环会一直持续到农场
So the cycle will continue until the ranch
被缩减到最不值钱的部分
is whittled down to its least valuable parts.
然后你就死了
Then you'll die,
凯斯和泰特绝对不可能
and there will be no way for Kayce and certainly not Tate
以此为生
to make a living from it...
就这样  七代人的传承
and just like that, seven generations
将被刻在小农场上
of our family legacy will be carved into little ranchettes,
人们来避暑时
where people will spend the summer
会好奇在他们来之前
wondering what this place looked like
还是我们家土地的时候  这里长什么样
before they got there when it was ours.
你说的每个字我都信  亲爱的
I don't doubt a word you're saying, honey. Not one.
但我
But I...
我不能卖
I can't sell it.
你不用卖掉农场  爸  只是土地
You wouldn't be selling the ranch, Dad, just the land--
一寸都不行
Not an inch. Not one.
这是他求我的最后一件事
It's the last thing he asked me.
-肯定还有别的办法  -没有了
- There's gotta be another way. - There isn't.
不  总会有办法的
Nah, there's always another way.
别让傲气影响你的决定  爸
Please don't let pride factor into this decision, Dad.
这件事太大了
It's just too big.
不是傲气  亲爱的  只是
No pride, honey. It's just...
我发过誓
I made a promise.
我宁愿失去土地也不想违背誓言
And I'd rather lose it than break it.
他宁愿
And he'd rather...
他也宁愿让我失去土地
He'd rather me lose it too.
我去睡觉了  亲爱的
I think I'm gonna turn in for the evening, honey.
好的
Okay.
黄石
达顿农场
请给我们两罐"黄夹克"
Could we get a couple Yellow Jackets, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
为你的夫妻生活  干杯
To your life with her. Cheers.
你在笑
You're smiling.
闭嘴吧
Shut up, will ya?
你做了一件没人能做到的事  里普
Well, you know, you did something that no one does, Rip.
你走出了过去
You've outlived your past.
也许吧  罗伊德
Maybe so, Lloyd. Maybe so.
*带我去见巫毒女王*
*Take me to see the voodoo queen*
*让她对我施咒*
*Let her put a spell on me*
*一点改变来缓解我的痛苦*
*A little bit of change to ease my pain*
*释放一个年轻人*
*Gonna set a young man free*
*我去过你家乡*
*I've been down through your hometown*
*在这片遥远的土地上*
*And all across this distant land*
他应该已经死了啊
He's supposed to be dead.
*亲爱的  我要走了*
*Honey, I'll be gone*
*告诉我妈我很想她*
*Tell my mother I miss her so*